Transcript: spscriptorium Sync: John Smith - forom.com
中文字幕 LiNuXyOuXia 双语合成 Lv&daisy
第11季13集 “断背吉他”
Episode 11x13 "Guitar Queer-O"
人生路茫茫，欲去乐园，放纵身心
I'm going out to South Park gonna have myself a time
友好的脸庞到处是，人们谦逊从不恼
Friendly faces everywhere humble folks without temptation
常事不如意，欲去乐园，远离烦恼
I'm goin out to south park gonna leave my woes behind
空闲的车位日夜有，人们滔滔拉家常
Ample parking day or night people spouting howdy neighbor
终日混沌沌，驶去乐园，去除疲惫
I'm heading out to south park to see if i cant unwind
丰满的女孩我喜欢,双峰绣乳真令我迷
I like girls with big fat titties really big fat titties
so来到乐园，去瞧衰友
So come on out to south park and meet some friends of mine
Stan，你们两家伙还真行啊！
Stan, you guys are good!
Sharon,孩子们在干吗呢？
Sharon, what are the boys doing?
哦，Stan和Kyle一起买了个新电视游戏
Oh, Stan and Kyle bought a new video game together.
他们现在会弹吉他了？ -哦，不，那不过是些破塑料控制器罢了
They can play guitar now? - No, they're just little plastic controllers.
按下五彩的按钮，游戏中就会弹奏吉他曲目
You hit the colored buttons and it makes the guitar track on the game play.
如果他们能花一半时间学真正的吉他，如同玩那游戏一样
If they spent half the time learning a real instrument as they do playing that game,
天晓得他们能达到啥成就 -啊，哈。
who knows what they could accomplish. - Hey yeah.
伙计们，听听那画面中人群的呐喊！ 他们爱我们！
Dude, listen to that video crowd! They love us!
那么说，你们男孩喜欢这音乐，是吗？ -当然喽，伙计。这是《吉他英雄》
So you boys like this music, huh? - Yeah, dude. It's Guitar Hero.
Stan和Kyle玩这游戏真有一套啊！
Stan and Kyle are really good at it.
好吧，想见识下真正牛逼的事吗？瞧仔细了！
Well you kids wanna see something really cool? Check this out.
曾经，我从嘈杂迷惑之土升起
Once, I rose above the noise and confusion.
只愿在这幻想之外一瞥为快
Just to get a glimpse beyond this illusion.
我翱翔在天际，愈发高远
I was soaring ever higher
但我飞得太高了
but I flew too high.
尽管目仍可视，我... -老爸？老爸！瞎搞啥鬼事呢？
Though my eyes could see I- - Dad? Dad! What are you doing?!
其实，我可以用真正的吉他弹奏很多歌曲
I can actually play a lot of these songs on a real guitar.
想学吗？我教你们
You want me to teach you boys how?
那太放荡了，Marsh先生 -同感，太TM傻冒了！
That's gay, Mr. Marsh. - Yeah, that's stupid, Dad.
但这才是真正的吉他 -真正的吉他只适合老不死去玩
But this is real. - Real guitars are for old people.
先生，你很在意吗？ 我们就想看看Stan和Kyle一起玩
Do you mind, sir? We wanna watch Stan and Kyle play.
好吧，这次我们试试冲击60,000分大关
Alright, let's try to score 60,000 points this time.
准备好了吗？
Are you ready to rock?
坚持努力，我任性的儿子
Carry on my wayward son
大功告成之时，一切欢喜
There'll be peace when you are done
放下疲惫的头脑，躺下僵硬的身体，好好休息
Lay your weary head to rest
不是不哭了吗
Don't you cry no more
游戏结束！你个大衰仔！
Game over! You suck!
哈，他们成功在望！
They're gonna do it!
伙计们，来吧，这次冲100，000分大关！
Come on, guys, a hundred thousand points!
Cartman,你丫闭嘴。我们需要聚精会神
Cartman, shut up. We're concentrating.
你们打破的100，000分大关！
You have broken a hundred thousand points!
你们是摇滚巨星！
You are rock stars!
嘿，伙计，我们现在彻头彻尾是摇滚巨星了！
Dude, we are total rock stars now!
你们才不是啥摇滚巨星！ 那不过是个破不拉叽的塑料玩意儿！
You're not rock stars! This is just a stupid plastic controller!
等会儿。
Hang on.
是Stan Marsh吗？ -啥事？
Stan Marsh? - Yeah?
我是Charles Kincaid， 来自Kincaid人才中介
I'm Charles Kincaid, from the Kincaid Talent Agency?
我刚刚听说你打破了吉他英雄100，000分纪录
I just heard you broke a hundred thousand points on Guitar Hero.
恩，是我们搞掂的 -太令我印象深刻了
Yeah, we did. - Well, I'm impressed.
还有我想做你的经纪人 -哇喔，当真？
And I'd like to be your manager. - Wow, really?
伙计！伙计，Kyle，这人想做咱经纪人
Dude! Dude, Kyle, this guy wants to be our manager!
没门！ -你是认真的？
No way! - For reals?
获得100，000分真是惊为天人， 但我考虑更多的是凭你们的真正实力该争取的目标
Scoring a hundred thousand points is amazing, but I think with the right label behind you,
你两能够打破1，000，000分！ -真TM屌！
you boys could make a million points. - That'd be awesome!
那么，我们谈成了？
So, we're in business then?
那，你觉得怎么样？ -我喜欢这调调。那俩男孩弹的？
Well, what do you think? - I like it. That's these boys playing?
不，不，那是Kansas弹的
No, that's Kansas.
但那俩男孩在双人合作专家模式下用这曲子破了100，000分
But these boys scored a hundred thousand points to it on Expert Level in Co-op Mode.
那真是惊为天人，刻骨铭心
That's pretty Goddamned impressive.
好吧，我们会和他们签一年合约的 -是的！孩子们，你们成功了。
Alright, we'll sign them to a one-year deal. - Yes! You did it, boys.
听着，孩子，今晚在我那宽敞的公寓里将会举行一场盛大的庆功宴
Listen, boys, I'm having a huge celebrity party at my giant mansion tonight.
为啥不作为我光荣的新星前来呢？
Why don't you come by as my honorary new artists?
忒酷！
Cool!
哇喔，好大的排场啊！
Wow, this is a huge party.
哦，对了，所有科罗拉多州的超级巨星都汇集于此
Oh yes, all the biggest stars in Colorado are here.
伙计，伙计，那是来自4频道播新闻的Ron Zappolo！
Dude, dude, that's Ron Zappolo from Channel 4 News!
哇喔！瞧瞧那边，是那位Jake Jabs
Wow! Oh, and look over there, that's that Jake Jabs guy
他来自过美国家具大卖场商业集团
from American Furniture Warehouse commercials.
大家听好了，挺好了，这是Stan和Kyle
Everyone? Everyone, this is Stan and Kyle.
他们刚刚在《吉他英雄》中打破了100,000分
They just broke a hundred thousand points on Guitar Hero.
请好好享受，这屋里有更多的饮料和美眉
Please enjoy yourselves, there's lots more coke and sex in the house.
伙计！快看，那边的是Jay Cutler！ 效力于丹佛·布隆球斯的四分卫！
Dude! Dude, that's Jay Cutler over there! Quarterback for the Denver Broncos!
哦，我的老天！ -想会会他吗？
Oh my God! - Would you boys like to meet him?
你是认真的？
Are you serious?
Jay，我想让你见见Stan和Kyle 他们刚在《吉他英雄》中破了100，000分
Jay, I want you to meet Stan and Kyle. They broke a hundred thousand points on Guitar Hero.
哇喔，真的？真高兴见到你俩 -也同样高兴见到你
Wow, really? Nice to meet you guys. - Nice to meet you!
我是说，就你那衰样，我爸说 或许以后某日你才会来几脚精彩的
I mean, you kind of suck, but my dad says you might be good someday.
谢谢
Thanks.
Alex，你在某处见过我老婆吗？
Alex, have you seen my wife anywhere?
你们知道来自沙恩钻石商店集团的Tom Shane吗？
You boys know Tom Shane from the Shane Company Diamond Store commercials?
还用问吗？他TM是个传奇人物！
Do we? He's a legend!
你得记住这些孩子，Tom
You remember these boys, Tom.
他们几周后将在街机厅现在打破1,000,000分
They're gonna break a million points live at the video arcade in a few weeks.
那将会，惊天地，泣鬼神
That, would be impressive.
伙计，我们成了。我们是超星，又酷又帅
Dude, we've arrived. We're super, awesome and cool.
是啊。时来运转，衰运终于TMD跑光了
Yeah. Life is finally going to not suck so hard for us.
你是摇滚巨星！
You Rock!
好啊，孩子们，排演太精彩了
All right, nice rehearsal, boys.
伙计，中途我完全恼了哎！ 没瞧见吗？
Dude, I totally miffed that middle part. Did you see that?
是哎，伙计，那段儿几乎是不可能的任务 -那太酷了，孩子们
Yeah dude, that's almost impossible. - That was real cool, kids.
嘿，Kyle，我车里有个不同的控制器 也许会对你有帮助
Hey, Kyle, there's a different controller in my car that might work better for you.
为什么不和Jim一起去 他会帮你找到那玩意的
Why don't you go with Jim and he'll help you find it.
哦，好的。太棒了
Oh, okay. Cool.
孩子，你有真正的潜力 我坚信不移，你能拿下1,000,000分
You've got real potential, kid. I have no doubt you can break a million.
当真？在拍我马屁吧？ -我当真认为你行
Really? That'd be sweet. - I think you could.
但至于你的朋友呢，厄，说实话 我认为他在拖你后腿
But as for your friend, well, to be honest, I think he's holding you back.
什么，啥？你是说——Kyle?
What, you mean, Kyle?
瞧瞧，你得分比他高多了 谁更强显而易见
Look, you score a lot higher than him. There's no question who the better one is.
我打算让你会会其他玩家
I wanna put you with some other players,
为你找个好搭档，帮助你提高成绩
find a partner for you who can really help you max your score.
但Kyle和我一直一起玩 我们一起合资买了这游戏套件
But, Kyle and I always play together. We both chipped in for the game system.
你很高尚。 但你认为《吉他英雄》哪点捕获了你的忠心？
Very honorable. But you know where loyalty gets you in a game like Guitar Hero?
没啥别的，听听那电视里呐喊的人群
Nowheres. Just listen to that video crowd.
好久没在电视里听到如此狂野的呐喊了
I haven't heard a video crowd go that wild in a long time.
你有机会破1,000,000分大关
You've got a chance to score a million points,
而且我不希望你放弃它，仅因在意好友的感受
and I hate to see you throw it away because you're worried about your friend's feelings.
你会爱上这小子的，Stan。 他是我见过最优秀的《吉他英雄》玩家之一
You're gonna love this kid, Stan. He's one of the best Guitar Hero players I've ever seen.
当然除你之外
Except for you, of course.
嘿，Thad!
Ah, Thad!
Stan Marsh，这位是Thad Jarvis -吃了吗？
Stan Marsh, this is Thad Jarvis. - Sup?
这位Thad已经辅助了无数伟大的《吉他英雄》玩家 对吗，Thad?
Thad here has backed up a lot of really great Guitar Hero players. Isn't that right, Thad?
嗯
Yup.
他甚至连游戏系统都不用。 靠听的就能玩《吉他英雄》
He doesn't even need a game system to play on. He can play Guitar Hero acoustically.
不错，但他会弹专家级的Buckethead
Yeah, but can he play Buckethead on Expert Level?
放手干吧，Thad。给他秀两手
Go ahead, Thad. Show him what you can do.
瞧仔细了
Check this out.
天杀的强，对吗？
Pretty damn good, huh?
是的，那简直素神！ 但你会弹"John the Fisherman"吗？
Yeah, that's pretty good. But can you play "John the Fisherman"?
Stan，这孩子去跟你合作 你将会写下《吉他英雄》史上新的一章
Stan, with this kid backing you, you're gonna make Guitar Hero history.
噢，我太爱这调了！
Oh, I love this song.
瓦靠，看看他那屌样！
Wow wee, look at him go!
嘿伙计，怎么.....?
Hey dude, how'd it-?
Kyle
Kyle.
我还以为你病了
I thought you were sick.
这位兄台贵姓？
Who is this?
这位是Thad Jarvis -吃了吗？
This is Thad Jarvis. - Sup?
这TM怎么回事，Stan? -Kyle,我本打算慢慢跟你说
What's going on, Stan? - Kyle, I was gonna tell you later.
Kincaid先生认为我该先和Thad练一段时间
Mr. Kincaid thinks I should play with Thad for a while.
但这是我们的游戏。咱一起买的！
But it's our game. We bought it together.
我了解，还，还有我想公平起见 所以我会买下你的那份的
I know, and, and I wanna be fair about it, so, I'll buy you out of your part.
让我拿钱走人？你TM说啥呢？
Buy me out?! What are you saying?!
是什么让你爽到极点？ 很好很强大，你TM竟让我拿钱走人
What makes you so high and mighty you can buy me out?!
别这么说我，Kyle! -哦老天，这太TM屌了！
Don't put this all on me, Kyle! - Oh my God this is so awesome.
你午后不久就被吹着凉了
You were the one that's been blowing off playing after midnight,
不继续练习是因为你病了 -我想吐了！
not playing because you were sick. - I have been sick!
你看，问题是我再也不会和你一起合作破1,000,000分了
Look, the point is I'm never gonna break a million points playing with you!
明知故问！
You know that's true!
我想，我之前一直没想过这恰恰和得分有关
I guess I didn't realize it was just about the points.
伙计，这游戏有规则
Dude, this game rules.
继续干，明白了吗？
Let's just do this, all right?
嘿！你是那个买了我《吉他英雄》的孩子吧？ 感觉如何？
Hey! You're the kid I sold the Guitar Hero game to. How are you liking it?
我想还不错 但我需要点那游戏的指导书籍
It's okay, I guess. But I need some game guides for it.
我的经纪人和赞助商在街机厅 做了现场演奏的准备
My manager and producer set up this live thing at the video arcade
我猜在那儿，所有人面前，攻取1,000,000分 并且我，我紧张坏了！
where I'm supposed to break a million in front of everybody and I'm I'm stressing out.
同感，《吉他英雄》可能是十分具有紧张感
Yeah, Guitar Hero can be pretty stressful.
但或许你明白，也许忘了那指导书
But you know, maybe instead of a game guide,
你更应该就买一款游戏来缓解你的压力
you should just buy another game to kind of ease the stress.
你听说过《海洛因勇士》吗? -海洛因勇士？
Have you ever heard of Heroin Hero? - Heroin Hero?
那是款相当惬意的游戏
It's a way easier game.
你仅需做的就是在魔法丛林里来回奔跑 并注射假海洛因
All you do is run around a magical forest and shoot simulated heroin.
你或许可以叫它，终极第一人称射击游戏
You could call it the ultimate first-person shooter.
那么游戏里没得分？没人群？
And there's no score? No crowds?
没有人类。你仅需做的就是跑遍那美丽的丛林 去追捕一只巨龙
No man. All you do is run through the pretty forest and chase a big dragon.
但你永不必抓到那龙 你仅仅需要继续追捕就行了
But you don't ever catch the dragon. You just keep chasing it.
抓吧，来吧，这边走 射啊，你会抓住我的
Chase me. Come on. This way. Shoot up and then you can catch me.
上啊！
Come on.
靠，这太屌了！
Dude, this is awesome.
他们干得怎么样？
How are they coming?
无须担心，Hart先生。 他们这几天里就会为那表演秀做好准备
No worries, Mr. Hart. They'll be ready for the big show in a few days.
他们最好能。我可是花了笔巨款去包场的
They'd better be. I paid good money to rent this place out.
操天杀的！
Damnit!
伙计，真衰！你昨晚上练了吗？ -当然，我昨晚上当然练了！
Dude, suck. Did you practice last night? - Yeah, I practiced last night!
闭上你那臭嘴继续弹！
Just shut up and play!
不，你知道个屁？！试试这曲子！
No, you know what?! Screw this!
我才不弹这曲子呢！你干啥选这破曲啊？！
I'm not playing this song! Why did you pick this stupid song?!
Stan，这是我们一致认定你该弹的曲子。
Stan, it's the song we all agreed you would play.
是吗？好吧，我TM改主意了！ 我们换Cheap Trick!
Yeah? Well I changed my mind! We're changing the song to Cheap Trick!
没门儿！我恨那屎臭般的“泡泡糖”摇滚乐！
No way. I hate that bubblegum crap.
是吗？好吧，你TM不是领队，不是吗，Thad? 我爱啥啥！
Yeah? Well you're not the leader, are you, Thad?! We play the music I wanna play!
Stan,你干啥满口怨气，粗暴待人啊？
Stan, why are you so grumpy-grouchy?
我爱啥啥！ 并且我将会换首不同的曲子！
We're playing what I want and I'll select a different song!
好吧？那么这首咋样？
Yeah? Well how about this one?
我TM不干了
I quite.
我走人，不干了，跑路了，不管了
I quit I quit I quit. I quit.
不管了，跑路了，不干了，走人了
你晓得个屁？！ 我才是伟人，Thad
You know what? That's great with me, Thad.
因为我TM不需要你就能拿下1,000,000分！
Because I don't need you to break a million points!
我以前还从没做到过！
I never did!
Stan,你TM瞎搞啥呢？ －我只是想一个人弹，不行吗？
Stan, what is the matter with you? - I just wanna play alone, alright?!
我实在无法把精力一直放在那些把我当驴使的烂屁眼身上！
I can't concentrate with all these assholes riding me all the time!
这是啥？
What is this?
不妙噢....
Man...
你一直在玩《海洛因勇士》？ -就，就玩了一会儿
Are you playing Heroin Hero? - Just, just a little.
不！没人能就玩了一会儿《海洛因勇士》！ 你晓得的，你永远抓不住那条龙！
No! Nobody plays Heroin Hero just a little! You know, you never catch the dragon!
我知道，但它一直在叫唤我呢，不行吗？！
I know, but it mellos me out, okay?!
你最好集中心思
You'd better pull your act together,
因为现在你将一个人去破1,000,000分，并解锁超星领域
because now you're gonna have to break a million points and unlock superstardom solo!
灭问题！
No problem.
嘿，该走了，小不点！我们现在想玩！ －我还没完呢！
Hey, beat it, kid! We wanna play now! - I'm not done yet.
嘿，我认得你。你是Kyle Broflovski
Hey, I know you. You're Kyle Broflovski.
你以前不是有自己的《吉他英雄》套件吗？
Didn't you used to have your own Guitar Hero game system?
哦，不，你说的是别人 -好吧，看来是
No. You're thinking of somebody else. - Yeah, sure.
他是那个拿下100,000分的孩子
He's the kid that scored a hundred thousand points.
怎么现在在这玩呢？ -瞧，上前去玩吧，行吗？
How come you're playing here now? - Look, just go ahead and play, alright?
让我一个人静静
Leave me alone.
我能要杯Fresca吗？
Can I get a Fresca, please?
你玩那游戏很有一套，孩子 像这样的邋遢地儿可配不上你
You're good at that game, Kid. Too good to be playing in a dump like this.
那么好吧，实际上我没钱再玩了 我四肢也都快麻了
Yeah well, I can't really afford to play anymore anyway. I'm about out of quarters.
那么这么着吧，也许我这个周末晚将用那玩意放放额外的音乐
Well look, maybe I can use some extra music playing to this thing on weekend nights.
你可以过来，在这打打小工，或许你还能免费玩
You come in, work around here a little and maybe you can play it for free.
我赞同你试着做的，Mick 但我可不是义演慈善家
I appreciate what you're trying to do, Mick, but I ain't a charity case yet.
啥义演慈善家？我不过是在试着帮帮你这个一时不走运的孩子罢了
Charity case, I'm just trying to help out a kid who's a little down on his luck is all.
万分感谢，Mick
Thanks, Mick.
快抓啊，上啊，抓吧
Catch me. Come on, catch me.
怎么了？跟着我啊，来吧
What's wrong? Follow me. Come on.
Marsh?Stan，你该......
Marsh? Stan, you got-
哦老天
Oh my God!
起来，Stan!给我醒醒！
Get up, Stan! Wake up!
嗯？干啥？
Huh? What?
你十分钟内就该出发了！ 大伙都前去看你呢！
You're going on in ten minutes! Everybody's coming to see you!
那龙，上哪了？
The dragon. Where did it go?
你给我清醒点！
You've gotta pull it together!
集中心思，操TM天杀的！
Pull it together, goddamnit!
感谢各位前来Gamecraft街机厅，观看Stan Marsh打破1,000,000分
Thank you for coming to Gamecraft Arcade to watch Stan Marsh break a million points
并解锁无人能及的超星领域
and unluck superstardom.
上啊，Stan! -好吧，Stan，成功在望。噢，不！
Go Stan! - All right, Stan, you've got it, man!
伙计，他出了啥鬼事？
Dude, what's the matter with him?
他三天三夜不睡觉，连续不断地玩《海洛因勇士》
He's been up for three days straight playing Heroin Hero.
加油，Stan!成功在望！
Come on, Stan! You got it!
操天杀的，他整个一傻冒！
Goddamnit, he's a mess!
噢，不，太残忍了，我看不下去了！
Oh man, I can't watch this.
你TM干啥呢？ 电视里的人群都开始喝倒彩了！
What are you doing?! The video crowd is starting to boo!
走吧，伙计们，离开这吧
Come on guys. Let's get out of here.
下次给我引荐啥人才时 好好用你的狗眼确认下到底有没有才！
The next time you bring me some talent, make sure they're talent-ed.
你毁了一切！你曾拥有一切却毁了它！ 听听那嘘声一片的人群！他们恨你！
You blew it! You had it all and you blew it! Listen to that video crowd! They hate you!
他在那儿！
There he is!
那么，你拿下了1,000,000分没？
So, did you break a million yet?
没，我没有破1,000,000分并打开超星领域 满意了吧？
No, I didn't break a million points and unlock superstardom, all right?
我被那破游戏整了！
I'm done with that stupid game!
厄，别闹了。你一旦开始玩《吉他英雄》 你就无法停止攀登顶峰的计划
Aw, come on. Once you start playing Guitar Hero, you can't stop till you reach the top.
我不过想找些别的游戏来玩
I just wanna find something else to play.
你玩过《复兴斗士》吗？
Have you played Rehab Hero?
你将被一条巨龙追捕 但你一直在前面逃跑
You get chased by a big dragon, but you keep running away from it.
我不过想要个画面靓丽的操作简单的赛车游戏 如何？
I just want a nice, simple driving game. How about that?
当然行，孩子。当然可以
Sure kid. Sure.
好吧，那曾是Splendifs的曲子 而现在这儿是一首众所周知，轰动一时的曲子
All right, that was the Splendifs. And now here's a hit you all remember.
这首是当地两个四年级男孩在《吉他英雄》里拿下100,000分的曲子
It's the song that two local fourth grade boys scored a 100.000 points to on Guitar Hero.
不知道那俩男孩发生了什么 我想他们再也不会碰这游戏了
Don't know whatever happened to those boys. I guess they're not playing the game anymore.
雨在空中倾泻而下，我醒了过来
Woke up to the sound of pouring rain
风在耳边沉吟低语，我想起了你
The wind would whisper and I'd think of you
泪水淌下你的脸，滴滴如在呼唤我
And all the tears you cried, that called my name
Kyle，能给我5分钟讲个话吗？
Kyle, could I just talk to you for like five minutes?
你在这又干啥呢？ -求你了，不会耽搁太久的
What are you doing here? - Please, it won't take long.
操天杀的。我们去作短暂休息，5分钟内回来
Goddamnit. We're gonna take a short break. Be back in five.
我刚刚听你弹了会儿 伙计，你当真强了很多
I was listening to you for a while. Dude, you've gotten a lot better.
哦，谢了！我曾经是如此热切的渴望你对我能力的认同
Oh, thank you! I was so eagerly awaiting your approval of my abilities!
你看，Kyle，游戏设备仍设在我家里然后....
Look, Kyle, the game is still set up at my house and...
也许我们能够试着再在那儿玩
maybe we could go try playing it again over there.
哦，这么说，那位豪侠的骑士现在来救我于平庸市井之中了！
Oh, so the gallant knight now comes to rescue me from the bowels of mediocrity!
哦，感谢啊，你那王者的风范！
Oh, thank you, your royal lordship!
根本不是那么回事儿！
That isn't it at all.
你不会成功的，Stan! 我现在能在这儿随心所欲地玩
You don't get it, Stan! I can play here all I want.
我甚至能拿免费的Frescas 我才不需要你呢！
I even get free Frescas. I don't need you anymore!
我明白。但我需要你
I know. I need you.
我想我当初有一段美好的时光 是因为我与经纪人签了合约然后.....
I thought I was having a great time because I was getting signed by managers and...
去了那美女如云，食品丰盛的盛大派对， 但后来我意识到...
going to big sex and coke parties, but then I realized...
我很高兴是因为我一直和的挚友在一起
I was having fun because I was doing all that with my best friend.
那很有趣，难道不是吗？
It was pretty fun, wasn't it?
是啊
Yeah.
瞧，总之恐怕我们能拿下1,000,000分
Look, I doubt we could break a million together anyway.
我才不关心那鸟事 我只不过想和你再次玩罢了
I don't care. I'd just like to play with you again.
为了玩耍的乐趣
For the fun of it.
我还真没瞧见，不彻底地踢踢游戏英雄榜的屁眼，有何乐趣！
I don't really see the fun in not trying to kick that game's ass once and for all!
啥，你说那事？ -我认为我们能办到，Stan
What, you mean it? - I think we can do it, Stan.
我一个人已经好几次接近1,000,000分了
I've been close to a million a few times by myself.
那么出发吧，伙计！
Then let's go, dude!
哦，等等，等会儿，我本该在这儿弹的
Oh wait. Wait, I'm supposed to play here.
嘿，Mick，你介意我出去溜达会儿吗？
Hey, Mick, would you mind if I stepped out for a sec?
去吧，孩子，离开这儿吧 又有谁需要你在这嚎叫着摇滚？
Go on, get out of here, kid. Who needs your wailing and rocking around here anyways?
谢了，Mick!
Thanks, Mick!
好吧，伙计，一起去干吧！
All right, dude, let's do this.
TMD啥鬼事？
What the hell?
来啊，上啊。你几乎抓到我了
Come on, come on. You almost got me.
抓我啊，来啊
Catch me. Come on.
操天杀的！老爸，从我们的Xbox前滚蛋！ -表烦我，我几乎抓到了那龙
Goddamnit! Dad, get off our X-Box! - Hang on, I almost caught the dragon.
呵呵，你差不多抓到我了
Hehe, you almost caught me.
不，我和Kyle将要玩《吉他英雄》！
No, me and Kyle are gonna play Guitar Hero!
我一定能抓住它！等等！现在它上哪了？ -你永远抓不到那龙，老爸！
I can get him! Wait! Where's he going now? - You don't ever catch the dragon, Dad!
不，不，我说过，我才是你老爸！ 给我弄回来！
No! No, I said! I am your father! Put it back on!
老妈，你能把老爸拖出这儿吗？
Mom, will you get Dad out of here?
表给我作弊，Craig! -那有算啥门子的作弊！
Stop cheating, Craig! - How was that cheating!
因为你竟敢戏弄我，你个非洲碳黑臭屁眼！
Because you tricked me, you black asshole!
快讯！快讯！
Fellas! Fellas!
他们要成了！ -啥？
They're gonna do it! - What?
Stan和Kyle！他们几乎将打破《吉他英雄》1,000,000分 并解锁超星领域！
Stan and Kyle! They're about to break a million on Guitar Hero and unlock superstardom!
哦，走！来吧，大家走！
Oh, let's go! Cone on, let's go!
他们成功在望！
They're gonna do it!
他们干成了！ -哦，我那性感的，耶，耶稣啊！
They did it! - Oh my sweet J-Jesus!
你们足够耐心将《吉他英雄》玩到了1,000,000分！
You have played Guitar Hero enough to reach one million points!
恭喜你们！
Congratulations!
你们
You.
是
Are.
断背男！
Fags.
那算啥门子东西？
That's it?
我操他妈的OB呸！
Goddamnit!
操他妈祖宗十八代！
God damnit!
Butters，接下来想和我玩玩“断背”吗？
Butters, you wanna play me next?
好啊，但我会在性交毒友会后偷汉子的
Okay, but I get to be the one that betrays you after the sex and drug party.